{ 
    "name":  "Irregular Verb PT ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ / EN ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§", 
    "description":  "Creates a card for each conjugation of the verb and their reverse. Generates 10 cards.", 
    "form":  """
        <label for='pt_inf'>PT ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Infinitive</label>
        <input type='text' name='pt_inf' value='{{ pt_inf }}'>

        <label for='eng_inf'>EN ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ Infinitive</label>
        <input type='text' name='eng_inf' value='{{ eng_inf }}'>

        <label for='I'>ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ I..</label>
        <input type='text' name='I' value='{{ I }}'>

        <label for='you'>ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ You..</label>
        <input type='text' name='you' value='{{ you }}'>

        <label for='he'>ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ He/She..</label>
        <input type='text' name='he' value='{{ he }}'>

        <label for='eu'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Eu..</label>
        <input type='text' name='eu' value='{{ eu }}'>

        <label for='tu'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Tu...</label>
        <input type='text' name='tu' value='{{ tu }}'>

        <label for='ele'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ VocÃª/Ele/Ela</label>
        <input type='text' name='ele' value='{{ ele }}'>

        <label for='nos'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ NÃ³s</label>
        <input type='text' name='nos' value='{{ nos }}'>

        <label for='eles'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ VocÃªs/Eles/Elas</label>
        <input type='text' name='eles'  value='{{ eles }}'>
        """, 
    "preview":  "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ pt_inf }} / ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ {{ eng_inf }}", 
    "cards":  {
        'eu': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ eu }}', 'answer': 'I {{ I }}'},
        'tu': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ tu }}', 'answer': 'You {{ you }}'},
        'ele': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ ele }}', 'answer': 'He/She {{ he }}'},
        'nos': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ nos }}', 'answer': 'We {{ you }}'},
        'eles': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ eles }}', 'answer': 'They {{ you }}'},
        'I': {'question': 'ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ I {{ I }}', 'answer': '{{ eu }}'},
        'you': {'question': 'ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ You {{ you }}', 'answer': '{{ tu }}'},
        'he': {'question': 'ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ He/She {{ he }}', 'answer': '{{ ele }}'},
        'we': {'question': 'ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ We {{ you }}', 'answer': '{{ nos }}'},
        'they': {'question': 'ğŸ‡¬ğŸ‡§ They {{ you }}', 'answer': '{{ eles }}'},
    },
}


{ 
    "name":  "Irregular Verb PT ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ / IT ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹", 
    "description":  "The same card and its reverse is rendered with a random conjugation of the verb. Produces 2 cards.", 
    "form":  """
        <label for='pt_inf'>PT ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Infinitive</label>
        <input type='text' name='pt_inf' value='{{ pt_inf }}'>

        <label for='it_inf'>IT ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Infinitive</label>
        <input type='text' name='it_inf' value='{{ it_inf }}'>

        <label for='io'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Io..</label>
        <input type='text' name='io' value='{{ io }}'>

        <label for='tu_it'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Tu..</label>
        <input type='text' name='tu_it' value='{{ tu_it }}'>

        <label for='lui'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Lui/Lei..</label>
        <input type='text' name='lui' value='{{ lui }}'>

        <label for='noi'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Noi..</label>
        <input type='text' name='noi' value='{{ noi }}'>

        <label for='loro'>ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ Loro..</label>
        <input type='text' name='loro' value='{{ loro }}'>

        <label for='eu'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Eu..</label>
        <input type='text' name='eu' value='{{ eu }}'>

        <label for='tu_pt'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ Tu...</label>
        <input type='text' name='tu_pt' value='{{ tu_pt }}'>

        <label for='ele'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ VocÃª/Ele/Ela</label>
        <input type='text' name='ele' value='{{ ele }}'>

        <label for='nos'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ NÃ³s</label>
        <input type='text' name='nos' value='{{ nos }}'>

        <label for='eles'>ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ VocÃªs/Eles/Elas</label>
        <input type='text' name='eles'  value='{{ eles }}'>
    """, 
    "preview":  "ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ pt_inf }} / ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ {{ it_inf }}", 
    "cards":  {
        'eu': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ eu }}', 'answer': '{{ io }}'},
        'tu_pt': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ tu_pt }}', 'answer': '{{ tu_it }}'},
        'ele': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ ele }}', 'answer': '{{ lui }}'},
        'nos': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ nos }}', 'answer': '{{ noi }}'},
        'eles': {'question': 'ğŸ‡µğŸ‡¹ {{ eles }}', 'answer': '{{ loro }}'},
        'io': {'question': 'ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ {{ io }}', 'answer': '{{ eu }}'},
        'tu_it': {'question': 'ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ {{ tu_it }}', 'answer': '{{ tu_pt }}'},
        'lui': {'question': 'ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ {{ lui }}', 'answer': '{{ ele }}'},
        'noi': {'question': 'ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ {{ noi }}', 'answer': '{{ nos }}'},
        'loro': {'question': 'ğŸ‡®ğŸ‡¹ {{ loro }}', 'answer': '{{ eles }}'},
    },
}